Viewers, I know you are with us.
Distance is not a barrier for the grace of God.
The Bible says whatever you ask in my name shall be given.
Right now, I command that demon to leave you,
that demon to leave your body, that sickness to leave your body!
You sickness, leave this body!
You demon, leave this body!
Leave this body!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Can you see the reflection?
Because those who hear the Word must be affected.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Those who are under the influence of this telecast, wherever you are,
right now, listen to me.
You are here, we are there.
Wherever you are, we are there.
Distance is not a barrier.
I lay hand upon you.
Demon, leave that body!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ, I lay hand upon you.
Demon, leave that body, in the name of Jesus!
Leave that man, in the name of Jesus!
Leave that woman, in the name of Jesus!
Demon knows he must submit to the name Jesus.
That sickness, leave that man, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever you are located – in their blood, kidneys, liver, bones, tendons -
wherever you are located, you affliction, leave that man, leave that woman,
leave that child, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
As I pray, I sense God's deliverance touching you.
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
I sense God's deliverance, I sense God's healing touching you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
It happened!
Receive!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Deliverance!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Healing!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus, for healing them.
In Jesus' name.
Listen to this:
I will attend to Your Word, Oh Lord.
Say to yourself, that is a covenant.
I will keep Your Word in my heart
for they are my life, healing, deliverance, blessing, prosperity and salvation, in Jesus' name.
Mean it!
Let me pray with you concerning your promise.
You promised to attend to His Word.
You have promised to keep His Word in your heart for they are your life, healing, deliverance
blessing, prosperity and salvation.
I pray the Lord strengthens you to keep your promise.
Keep your promise!
In the midst of humiliation, keep your promise.
In the midst of embarrassment, keep your promise.
In the midst of temptation, keep your promise.
In the midst of tribulation, keep your promise.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Don't forget, the Lord says, in this world there will be tribulation.
Cheer up, I have overcome!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Have you been touched by Jesus Christ by praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV?
Don't forget to send us your photos or video footage of what happened to you during the prayer -
for the glory of God!
Post your pictures or videos on Facebook, Twitter or Instagram using the hashtags –
#PrayWithTBJoshua, #DistanceIsNotABarrier or #TouchTheScreen
Alternatively, you can upload them to our testimony website – i.emmanuel.tv -
or send them via email to info@emmanuel.tv with the subject: 'TESTIMONY'.
Remember, distance is NOT a barrier to the Holy Spirit!